export const review = [
	{
		question: `List what did God made on each day of creation.`,
		answer: ``
	},
	{
		question: `List the Ten Commandments.`,
		answer: ``
	},
	{
		question: `List the Whole Armor of God.`,
		answer: ``
	},
	{
		question: `List the Fruit of the Spirit.`,
		answer: ``
	}
];

export const general = [
	/* From trivia time */
	{
		question: `Who were the first man and woman?`,
		answer: `Adam and Eve`
	},
	{
		question: `What was the name of the good tree in the Garden of Eden?`,
		answer: `The tree of life`
	},
	{
		question: `What was the name of the bad tree in the Garden of Eden?`,
		answer: `The tree of the knowledge of good and evil`
	},
	{
		question: `What did Adam and Eve do wrong?`,
		answer: `Ate the fruit God said not to eat`
	},
	{
		question: `What did God do to keep Adam and Eve out of the garden?`,
		answer: `Placed an angel with a fiery sword at the entrance`
	},
	{
		question: `Who were Adam and Eve's first two sons?`,
		answer: `Cain and Abel`
	},
	{
		question: `What did Cain do to Abel?`,
		answer: `Killed him`
	},
	{
		question: `What did Noah build?`,
		answer: `The Ark`
	},
	{
		question: `Who were Noah's sons?`,
		answer: `Shem, Ham, and Japheth`
	},
	{
		question: `How many of each kind of animal went on the ark?`,
		answer: `Seven of each clean animal, two of each unclean animal`
	},
	{
		question: `How did Noah know there was dry land again?`,
		answer: `He sent out a raven once and a dove three times`
	},
	{
		question: `What is the sign of God's promise that He wouldn't flood the whole earth again?`,
		answer: `Rainbows`
	},
	{
		question: `How did baby Moses' mommy save him?`,
		answer: `Floated him in a basket down the river`
	},
	{
		question: `What did God tell Moses to say to Pharoh?`,
		answer: `Let my people go that they may worship me`
	},
	{
		question: `Through what did God speak to Moses?`,
		answer: `Burning bush`
	},
	{
		question: `What were some of the plauges of Egypt?`,
		answer: `Water into blood, frogs, lice, flies, sick livestock, boils, hail and fire, locusts, darkness, death of firstborn`
	},
	{
		question: `What did the Israelites follow out of Egypt?`,
		answer: `A pillar of cloud by day and fire by night`
	},
	{
		question: `What did God tell Moses to do to part the Red Sea?`,
		answer: `Raise his staff`
	},
	{
		question: `Why did Balaam's donkey leave the road?`,
		answer: `There was an angel in the way`
	},
	{
		question: `What did Balaam's donkey do when Balaam hit it?`,
		answer: `It asked, "Why are you hitting me?"`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was the really strong man?`,
		answer: `Samson`
	},
	{
		question: `What did Delila do to Samson?`,
		answer: `Cut his hair`
	},
	{
		question: `What happened to Samson after his hair was cut?`,
		answer: `He wasn't strong anymore`
	},
	{
		question: `What funny thing did Samson use to kill a thousand men?`,
		answer: `A donkey's jawbone`
	},
	{
		question: `What did they do to Samson after they put him in jail?`,
		answer: `Blinded him`
	},
	{
		question: `What was David's job as a boy?`,
		answer: `Shepherd`
	},
	{
		question: `What did David kill with his slingshot before he met Goliath?`,
		answer: `A bear and a lion`
	},
	{
		question: `How many stones did David take with him to face Goliath?`,
		answer: `5`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was David's best friend?`,
		answer: `Jonathan`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was Jonathan's dad?`,
		answer: `King Saul`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was the first king of Israel?`,
		answer: `King Saul`
	},
	{
		question: `What did David do to King Saul while he was sleeping?`,
		answer: `Took a corner of his robe`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was King Solomon's dad?`,
		answer: `King David`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was the prophet that made fun of the priests of Baal?`,
		answer: `Elijah`
	},
	{
		question: `What did Elijah say they should do to see who is the real god?`,
		answer: `Call for fire from heaven`
	},
	{
		question: `Did Baal send fire to burn up the priests' offering?`,
		answer: `No`
	},
	{
		question: `Did God send fire to burn up Elijah's offering?`,
		answer: `Yes`
	},
	{
		question: `When God sent fire to burn up Elijah's offering, what else did it do?`,
		answer: `Licked up the water`
	},
	{
		question: `How did Elijah go up into heaven?`,
		answer: `In a whirlwind`
	},
	{
		question: `What did Elisha see when Elijah went up into heaven?`,
		answer: `Chariots of fire`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was thrown into the fiery furnace?`,
		answer: `Shadrach, Meshach, and Abednego`
	},
	{
		question: `Who else was in the fiery furnace?`,
		answer: `An angel`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was thrown into the lions den?`,
		answer: `Daniel`
	},
	{
		question: `What did the lions do when Daniel was in the den?`,
		answer: `They didn't eat him`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was Jesus' mommy?`,
		answer: `Mary`
	},
	{
		question: `Who was Mary's husband?`,
		answer: `Joseph`
	},
	{
		question: `Who told Mary she was going to have a baby?`,
		answer: `The angel Gabriel`
	},
	{
		question: `What gifts did the wise men bring for Jesus?`,
		answer: `Gold, frankincense, and myrrh`
	},
	{
		question: `What was Jesus' first miracle?`,
		answer: `Turned water into wine`
	},
	{
		question: 'With what did Jesus feed 5,000 people?',
		answer: 'Five loaves of bread and two small fish'
	},
	{
		question: `How did Jesus calm the storm at sea?`,
		answer: `He said, "Peace, be still"`
	},
	{
		question: `Who betrayed Jesus?`,
		answer: `Judas Iscariot`
	},
	{
		question: `Who denied Jesus?`,
		answer: `Peter`
	},
	{
		question: `How did Jesus die?`,
		answer: `Nailed to a cross`
	},

	/* https://icebreakerideas.com/bible-trivia-questions-answers/ */
	{
		question: 'In what city was Jesus born?',
		answer: 'Bethlehem'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many books are in the New Testament?',
		answer: '27'
	},
	{
		question: 'What type of insect did John the Baptist eat in the desert?',
		answer: 'Locusts'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who were the first apostles called to follow Jesus?',
		answer: 'Peter and Andrew'
	},
	{
		question:
			'After Jesus was arrested, which apostle disowned him three times?',
		answer: 'Peter'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who recognized Jesus as the Messiah when he was presented at the Temple as a baby?',
		answer: 'Simeon'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who asked Pilate for Jesus’ body after the crucifixion?',
		answer: 'Joseph of Arimathea'
	},
	{
		question: 'Paul was shipwrecked on what island?',
		answer: 'Malta'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the shortest book in the New Testament?',
		answer: '2 John'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who is the author of the Book of Revelation?',
		answer: 'John'
	},
	{
		question: 'Matthew was a _________.',
		answer: 'Tax collector'
	},
	{
		question:
			'To what city was Saul traveling when he encountered a great and blinding light?',
		answer: 'Damascus'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who was the first person to come upon the injured man in the parable of the Good Samaritan?',
		answer: 'Priest'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Finish this verse. “In every battle you will need faith as your ______ to stop the fiery arrows aimed at you by Satan.”',
		answer: 'Shield'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Whose example does Paul say Christians should follow in Chapter 5 of Ephesians?',
		answer: 'Christ’s'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What does Paul say may “abound more and more in knowledge and in all judgment?”',
		answer: 'Love'
	},
	{
		question: 'What tribe is Paul from?',
		answer: 'Benjamin'
	},
	{
		question: 'According to the Beatitudes who will be filled?',
		answer: 'Those who hunger and thirst for righteousness'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What does Simon Peter do for a living before he becomes an apostle?',
		answer: 'He was a fisherman.'
	},
	{
		question:
			'In the Gospel of Mark, how does the Virgin Mary learn of her pregnancy?',
		answer: 'From the angel Gabriel'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who is Stephen in Acts of the Apostles?',
		answer: 'The first Christian martyr'
	},
	{
		question:
			'According to the Gospel of Matthew, who visits Jesus at his birth and where does this meeting take place?',
		answer: 'The three wise men, in a stable'
	},
	{
		question:
			'By what name is Paul of Tarsus known before he begins his missionary activity?',
		answer: 'Saul'
	},
	{
		question:
			'According to Paul’s formulation in 1 Corinthians, which is the greatest of the imperishable qualities?',
		answer: 'Love'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who is the high priest of Jerusalem who put Jesus on trial?',
		answer: 'Caiaphas'
	},
	{
		question:
			'In the Gospel According to John, which of the apostles doubts Jesus’s resurrection until he sees Jesus with his own eyes?',
		answer: 'Thomas'
	},
	{
		question:
			'According to the Gospel of Matthew, where does Jesus’s first public sermon take place?',
		answer: 'On the mount'
	},
	{
		question:
			'In the Gospel of John, for whom does Mary Magdalene mistake Jesus in his first resurrection appearance?',
		answer: 'Mary Magdalene'
	},
	{
		question:
			'How does Judas signal Jesus’s identity to the Roman officials?',
		answer: 'He kisses him.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who murders John the Baptist?',
		answer: 'Herod Antipas'
	},
	{
		question:
			'When Christians observe Palm Sunday, what biblical narrative are they celebrating?',
		answer: 'Jesus’s entry into Jerusalem before his death'
	},
	{
		question:
			'According to the Gospels, what is the unique literary genre Jesus employs to preach his message?',
		answer: 'The parable'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which Gospel is most concerned with the mystery and identity of the person of Jesus?',
		answer: 'John'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who baptizes Jesus?',
		answer: 'John the Baptizer'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who takes Jesus’s body off the cross?',
		answer: 'Joseph of Arimathea'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who is the first apostle to deny Jesus?',
		answer: 'Peter'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which Gospel is written by a doctor?',
		answer: 'Luke'
	},
	{
		question: 'Where was Jesus born?',
		answer: 'Bethlehem'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many apostles did Jesus have?',
		answer: '12'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the name of the disciple who betrayed Jesus?',
		answer: 'Judas Iscariot'
	},
	{
		question: 'How did Jesus die?',
		answer: 'He was crucified.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who gave Jesus gifts when he was born?',
		answer: 'The wise men'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who are the religious leaders who continually tried to trap Jesus with their questions?',
		answer: 'Pharisees'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the name of Jesus’ mother?',
		answer: 'Mary'
	},
	{
		question: 'What did Jesus do for Lazarus?',
		answer: 'Raised him from the dead'
	},
	{
		question: 'What job did Jesus’ earthly father, Joseph, do?',
		answer: 'Carpenter'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who wrote many of the letters to churches in the New Testament?',
		answer: 'Paul'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the collective name of the stories Jesus told?',
		answer: 'Parables'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who wanted to kill Jesus when he was a baby?',
		answer: 'Herod'
	},
	{
		question: 'What did Simon Peter do for a living?',
		answer: 'He was a fisherman.'
	},
	{
		question: 'What happened to Jesus after the resurrection?',
		answer: 'He ascended into heaven.'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What did the Holy Spirit look like when the disciples received it?',
		answer: 'Tongues of fire'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who went on missionary journeys to preach to the Gentiles?',
		answer: 'Paul'
	},
	{
		question: 'How did Paul escape from Damascus?',
		answer: 'In a basket down the city wall'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the last book of the New Testament?',
		answer: 'Revelation'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the name of Adam’s third son?',
		answer: 'Seth'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who was the mother of Samuel?',
		answer: 'Hannah'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What kind of bird brought Elijah food while he hid in the Kerith Ravine, east of Jordan?',
		answer: 'Ravens'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many books are there in the Old Testament?',
		answer: '39'
	},
	{
		question: 'In what language was the Old Testament written?',
		answer: 'Hebrew'
	},
	{
		question: 'What relation was Jacob to Abraham?',
		answer: 'Grandson'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many sons did Jacob (Israel) have?',
		answer: '12 – They formed the basis for the tribes of Israel.'
	},
	{
		question:
			'From which country did Moses help the Israelites escape from their lives of slavery?',
		answer: 'Egypt'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which tribe of Israel looked after the religious aspects of life?',
		answer: 'Levi'
	},
	{
		question:
			'On which day of the year could the High Priest enter the Holiest Place, the inner most part of the temple where the covenant box was kept?',
		answer: 'Day of Atonement'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Israel split into two kingdoms after the reign of King Solomon, with Israel in the north, but what was the name of the southern kingdom?',
		answer: 'Judah'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who was king of the southern kingdom when the northern kingdom of Israel fell to Assyria?',
		answer: 'Hezekiah'
	},
	{
		question:
			'The southern kingdom eventually fell also, but to which great power?',
		answer: 'Babylon'
	},
	{
		question:
			'After the exile, the Israelites returned and started to rebuild the temple in Jerusalem, but which other prophet along with Zechariah was sent to encourage the completion of the partly built temple?',
		answer: 'Haggai'
	},
	{
		question: 'One title of God is El Shaddai, which means what?',
		answer: 'Almighty God'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which king had the longest reign over the Kingdom of Israel?',
		answer: 'Jeroboam II'
	},
	{
		question: 'What does Israel mean?',
		answer: 'Prevails with God'
	},
	{
		question: 'In which prophecy do we read about the valley of dry bones?',
		answer: 'Ezekiel'
	},
	{
		question: 'How were sins forgiven in the Old Testament?',
		answer: 'Animal sacrifice'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is the name commonly given to the first five books of the Old Testament?',
		answer: 'Pentateuch'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who wrote the first five books of the Old Testament?',
		answer: 'Moses'
	},
	{
		question: 'What time period does the Old Testament cover?',
		answer: 'The beginning of man to the time of the Messiah'
	},
	{
		question: 'From which part of Adam’s body did God create Eve?',
		answer: 'Rib'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the first bird that Noah let out of the ark?',
		answer: 'Raven'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the name of Abraham’s nephew?',
		answer: 'Lot'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What did God ask Abraham to sacrifice to him on Mount Moriah?',
		answer: 'His only son'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What did Rachel steal from her father, Laban, when she left home with her husband Jacob?',
		answer: 'Laban’s household gods'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the name of Joseph’s youngest brother?',
		answer: 'Benjamin'
	},
	{
		question:
			'When Joseph was in prison, whose dream did he correctly interpret to mean he would be restored to his job?',
		answer: 'Butler'
	},
	{
		question: 'In what was baby Moses hidden?',
		answer: 'An ark of bulrushes'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the first plague the Lord sent on Egypt?',
		answer: 'Water turned into blood'
	},
	{
		question: 'On what mountain did Moses receive the law from God?',
		answer: 'Mount Sinai'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the ‘tabernacle’ for?',
		answer: 'To worship God in'
	},
	{
		question:
			'How did Rahab let the invading Israelites identify her house?',
		answer: 'She tied a red cord in the window'
	},
	{
		question: 'What weapons did Gideon use to defeat the Midianites?',
		answer: 'Trumpets, pitchers, and lamps'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which judge was betrayed to the Philistines by a woman?',
		answer: 'Samson'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who did Samuel anoint as the first King of Israel?',
		answer: 'Saul'
	},
	{
		question: 'How did David defeat Goliath?',
		answer: 'He threw a stone from his sling'
	},
	{
		question: 'How did Uriah die?',
		answer: 'David had him placed in the most dangerous spot in the battle.'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was Cain’s punishment for the murder of Abel?',
		answer:
			'He was banned from his occupation and made a restless wanderer on the earth.'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the secret of Samson’s great strength?',
		answer: 'He would lose his strength if his hair were cut.'
	},
	{
		question: 'What did Joseph’s brothers do to Joseph?',
		answer: 'They sold him into slavery.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who was Moses’ successor after his death?',
		answer: 'Joshua'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the name of David’s father?',
		answer: 'Jesse'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which prophet secretly anointed David as king?',
		answer: 'Samuel'
	},
	{
		question: 'How did the Jewish prophet Daniel end up in Babylon?',
		answer: 'He was taken captive in a raid by the Babylonian army.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Why does Cain kill his brother Abel?',
		answer:
			'Because God is more pleased by Abel’s sacrifice than by Cain’s.'
	},
	{
		question:
			'How does Jacob steal his brother, Esau’s, inheritance rights?',
		answer: 'By tricking his father with the help of his mother'
	},
	{
		question: 'From which catastrophe does Joseph save Egypt?',
		answer: 'Famine'
	},
	{
		question: 'How does God first appear to Moses?',
		answer: 'As a burning bush'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What object that God gives Moses allows him to perform signs and wonders?',
		answer: 'A wooden staff'
	},
	{
		question: 'How does God feed the Israelites in the desert?',
		answer: 'By a strange bread-like substance from heaven'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Why does Moses break the stone tablets inscribed with God’s commandments at Mount Sinai?',
		answer: 'Because the people are worshipping a golden idol'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Why does God curse the Israelites to wander the desert for forty years before entering the Promised Land?',
		answer: 'Because they did not believe that God would fight for them'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What do Moses and Joshua forbid the Israelites to do in the Promised Land?',
		answer: 'Intermarry with the native inhabitants'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who betrays Samson to the Philistines?',
		answer: 'Delilah'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What does David bring to Jerusalem to bless the religious city?',
		answer: 'The Ark of the Covenant'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What event triggers the division of Israel into two kingdoms?',
		answer:
			'Rehoboam wants the tribe of Judah to secede from the twelve tribes.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who is Elisha?',
		answer: 'Elijah’s apprentice and successor'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What do the deaths of King Ahab and his wife Jezebel have in common?',
		answer: 'Dogs eat the blood of their dead bodies.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which Jewish festival results from the events in Esther?',
		answer: 'Purim'
	},
	{
		question: 'What does King Solomon do in Israel?',
		answer: 'He builds a grand temple in Jerusalem.'
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is one of the main criteria in Leviticus for living in the Israelite camp?',
		answer: 'To be ceremonially clean'
	},
	{
		question: 'Why does God reprimand Job?',
		answer: 'Because Job heeds the advice of his friends'
	},
	{
		question: 'What did King Solomon ask for from God?',
		answer: 'Wisdom'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who wrote this line “The Lord is my Shepherd, I shall not want”?',
		answer: 'King David'
	},
	{
		question: 'What does “Eve” mean?',
		answer: '“mother of all living”'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who married Abraham?',
		answer: 'Sarah'
	},
	{
		question: 'Looking for a wife for Isaac, Abraham’s servant found:',
		answer: 'Rebekah'
	},
	{
		question: 'Jacob agreed to work 7 years for the hand of:',
		answer: 'Rachel'
	},
	{
		question:
			'This woman promised the Lord that if He would bless her with a son, she would dedicate the boy to Him. She later bore Samuel.',
		answer: 'Hannah'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who was David’s original wife?',
		answer: 'Michal'
	},
	{
		question:
			'This woman remained with her mother-in-law, Naomi, after Naomi’s husband and sons died.',
		answer: 'Ruth'
	},
	// {
	//   question:
	//     "This woman rumored that Joseph tried to commit adultery with her.",
	//   answer: "Potiphar’s wife"
	// },
	{
		question:
			'This harlot housed spies sent by Joshua to take the city of Jericho.',
		answer: 'Rahab'
	},
	{
		question: 'This woman married Moses.',
		answer: 'Zipporah'
	},
	// {
	// 	question:
	// 		'After David looked upon her lustfully, he had an affair with this woman that ultimately led to the death of her original husband.',
	// 	answer: 'Bathsheba'
	// },
	{
		question:
			'This woman tempted Samson to reveal the secret to his massive strength, which she used to betray him to the Philistines.',
		answer: 'Delilah'
	},
	{
		question:
			'This brave Israelite woman became queen of Persia and used her influence to protect her people, the Jews.',
		answer: 'Esther'
	},
	{
		question:
			'This woman was given to Jacob as a wife deceitfully before he could marry her younger sister.',
		answer: 'Leah'
	},
	// {
	//   question:
	//     "The prophet Hosea was commanded to marry this woman, though she was a harlot.",
	//   answer: "Gomer"
	// },
	{
		question:
			'This Egyptian woman was Sarah’s handmaiden, and bore Ishmael through Abraham.',
		answer: 'Hagar'
	},
	{
		question: 'This wicked queen wanted to kill the prophet Elijah.',
		answer: 'Jezebel'
	},
	{
		question: 'This woman gave birth to Moses.',
		answer: 'Jochebed'
	},
	{
		question:
			'This woman was turned into a pillar of salt because she looked back as Sodom and Gomorrah were being destroyed.',
		answer: 'Lot’s wife'
	},
	{
		question: 'This woman was Ruth’s sister-in-law.',
		answer: 'Orpah'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the first thing that God created?',
		answer: 'Light'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which day did God create plants?',
		answer: 'Third'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the boat Noah built called?',
		answer: 'An ark'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many of each type of animal did Noah have on the ark?',
		answer: 'Two'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the symbol of God’s promise to Noah?',
		answer: 'The rainbow'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who received the 10 commandments from God?',
		answer: 'Moses'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the name of Moses’ brother?',
		answer: 'Aaron'
	},
	{
		question: 'What food do we ask God to give us in the Lord’s Prayer?',
		answer: 'Bread'
	},
	{
		question:
			'People look on the outward appearance, but what does God look on?',
		answer: 'The heart'
	},
	{
		question: 'His father gave him a coat of many colors.',
		answer: 'Joseph'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who was thrown into a lions’ den by King Darius? This person prayed to God three times a day.',
		answer: 'Daniel'
	},
	{
		question: 'This young boy defeated a giant.',
		answer: 'David'
	},
	{
		question: 'This prophet was swallowed by a fish.',
		answer: 'Jonah'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who was the Son of God?',
		answer: 'Jesus'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the name of Jesus’ mother?',
		answer: 'Mary'
	},
	{
		question: 'What did Jesus’ father do for a job?',
		answer: 'Carpenter'
	},
	{
		question: 'Jesus told a parable about a prodigal _____.',
		answer: 'Son'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the shortest verse in the Bible?',
		answer: 'Jesus wept'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many disciples or apostles did Jesus have?',
		answer: 'Twelve'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which of the apostles betrayed Jesus?',
		answer: 'Judas'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is another name for the Sermon on the Mount?',
		answer: 'The beatitudes'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the name of the Sea where Jesus calmed a storm?',
		answer: 'The Sea of Galilee'
	}
];
